{
  "users": [
    {
      "email": "shann@gmail.com",
      "password": "$2a$10$FiSs56UgiWbFLKJkcdOqrOVXcdDJUgsePe6ZdGr5mnL89EYisH.Bu",
      "name": "shann",
      "quizHistory": [],
      "id": 1
    }
  ],
  "tests": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Basic Mathematics",
      "questionsList": [
        {
          "type": "single",
          "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 1",
          "options": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4"
          ],
          "answer": 2,
          "weight": 20
        },
        {
          "type": "single",
          "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 2",
          "options": [
            "4",
            "5",
            "6",
            "7"
          ],
          "answer": 3,
          "weight": 20
        },
        {
          "type": "single",
          "question": "What is the difference of 9 and 3",
          "options": [
            "3",
            "4",
            "5",
            "6"
          ],
          "answer": 4,
          "weight": 20
        },
        {
          "type": "single",
          "question": "What is the product of 4 and 2",
          "options": [
            "4",
            "5",
            "6",
            "7"
          ],
          "answer": 3,
          "weight": 20
        },
        {
          "type": "single",
          "question": "What is the quotient of 12 and 4",
          "options": [
            "2",
            "3",
            "4",
            "5"
          ],
          "answer": 2,
          "weight": 20
        }
      ],
      "totalWeight": 100
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "Basic English",
      "questionsList": [
        {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question": "I spoke to ____.",
          "options": [
            "He",
            "Him",
            "She",
            "Her"
          ],
          "answer": [
            2,
            4
          ],
          "weight": 20
        },
        {
          "type": "single",
          "question": "She Works ____ Saturday.",
          "options": [
            "at",
            "to",
            "in",
            "on"
          ],
          "answer": 4,
          "weight": 20
        },
        {
          "type": "single",
          "question": "How do you get to work? ____.",
          "options": [
            "By car",
            "In car",
            "By the car",
            "On car"
          ],
          "answer": 1,
          "weight": 20
        },
        {
          "type": "single",
          "question": "Do you like classical music? ____",
          "options": [
            "Yes, I likes",
            "Yes, I like",
            "Yes, I do",
            "Yes, I does"
          ],
          "answer": 3,
          "weight": 20
        },
        {
          "type": "single",
          "question": "He ---- born in 1963 in America.",
          "options": [
            "had",
            "is",
            "was",
            "did"
          ],
          "answer": 2,
          "weight": 20
        }
      ],
      "totalWeight": 100
    }
  ]
}